<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>🪴 Digital Garden</title>
      <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on 🪴 Digital Garden</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>Challenges on land cover change detection</title>
    <link>https:/quartz.jzhao.xyz/Challenges-on-land-cover-change-detection</link>
    <guid>https:/quartz.jzhao.xyz/Challenges-on-land-cover-change-detection</guid>
    <description>Previous research: Clouds could reduce the amount of usable data. It’s hard to find an ideal pair of Landsat images that are free of clouds, cloud shadows and snow Previous change detection algorithm over shorter time intervals has a limitations.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 15:39:44 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Phenology and sun angle differences in landsat data</title>
    <link>https:/quartz.jzhao.xyz/Phenology-and-sun-angle-differences-in-landsat-data</link>
    <guid>https:/quartz.jzhao.xyz/Phenology-and-sun-angle-differences-in-landsat-data</guid>
    <description> Phenology: Refers to the study of cyclic and seasonal natural phenomena, especially in relation to climate and plant and animal life. In the context of Landsat data, phenology affects the imagery because different seasons show varying characteristics of vegetation, water bodies, and other land features.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 15:34:44 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Welcome</title>
    <link>https:/quartz.jzhao.xyz/</link>
    <guid>https:/quartz.jzhao.xyz/</guid>
    <description>Hi, I’m Azka 👋🏼 § This is my digital garden built using Quartz. Currently reading Continuous Change Detection and Classification paper.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 15:29:11 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Continuous Change Detection and Classification</title>
    <link>https:/quartz.jzhao.xyz/Continuous-Change-Detection-and-Classification</link>
    <guid>https:/quartz.jzhao.xyz/Continuous-Change-Detection-and-Classification</guid>
    <description>It’s an algorithm used in remote sensing area for land cover analysis. The original methods published form paper titled “Continuous change detection and classification of land cover using all available Landsat data”, published in 11 February 2014.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 15:28:08 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>SpectralGPT</title>
    <link>https:/quartz.jzhao.xyz/SpectralGPT</link>
    <guid>https:/quartz.jzhao.xyz/SpectralGPT</guid>
    <description>Key takeaway § Universal remote sensing foundation model Trained on one million spectral remote sensing Sentinel-2 images 3 models (Million Parameters): Base (100M), large, (300M) huge (600M) 3D masking strategy, encoder for learning visual representation from spatial-spectral mixed tokens, decoder with multi-target reconstruction for preserving spectrally sequential characteristics Masked autoencoder (MAE) framework, masking rate 90% New benchmark dataset SegMunich, focuses on urban areas Pretrained: 700k data 12 spectral bands from fMoW-S2 200 epoch, 350k BigEarthNet Sentinel-2 100 epoch.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 15:10:22 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Impact of Land Cover on Environmental Processes</title>
    <link>https:/quartz.jzhao.xyz/Impact-of-Land-Cover-on-Environmental-Processes</link>
    <guid>https:/quartz.jzhao.xyz/Impact-of-Land-Cover-on-Environmental-Processes</guid>
    <description>Land cover influence the energy balance, carbon budget, and. hydrological cycle as many different physical characteristics change as a function of land cover, such as albedo, emissivity, roughness, photosynthetic capacity and transpiration.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 15:07:56 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Natural and Anthropogenic Land Cover Change</title>
    <link>https:/quartz.jzhao.xyz/Natural-and-Anthropogenic-Land-Cover-Change</link>
    <guid>https:/quartz.jzhao.xyz/Natural-and-Anthropogenic-Land-Cover-Change</guid>
    <description> Definition: Land cover change refers to the transformation of the physical and biological cover of the earth’s surface. Natural Causes: Climate Change: Alterations in temperature and precipitation patterns can transform landscapes, such as turning forests into grasslands.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 15:04:58 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Interpreting Time Series with CCDC</title>
    <link>https:/quartz.jzhao.xyz/Interpreting-Time-Series-with-CCDC</link>
    <guid>https:/quartz.jzhao.xyz/Interpreting-Time-Series-with-CCDC</guid>
    <description>GEE ability: access decades of imagery without the previous limitation of needing to download all the data to a local disk for processing Change Detection and Classification (CCDC) is a land change monitoring algorithm designed to operate on time series of satellite data.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 13:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Vim Key Bindings</title>
    <link>https:/quartz.jzhao.xyz/Vim-Key-Bindings</link>
    <guid>https:/quartz.jzhao.xyz/Vim-Key-Bindings</guid>
    <description>Vim is a highly customizable and efficient text editor that is popular among developers and power users. One of Vim’s standout features is its extensive set of keyboard shortcuts and commands, referred to as “key bindings.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 12:10:21 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>